孩子们 你们结婚的日子\n一定会是一生中最幸福的日子
Kids, your wedding day is supposed\nto be the happiest day of your life,
美好爱情的美好结局
the perfect ending to\na perfect love story.
我的婚礼--至少是我的第一个婚礼\n--却不那么尽如人意了
My wedding-- at least my first\nwedding-- didn't go so well.
回头想想 真是滑稽
It's funny looking back on it now.
我确定Stella就是我要娶的女人
I was so sure Stella was the one.
当她离开我 我崩溃了
And when she left me,\nI was so devastated.
但你们让我重振精神
But you guys got me through it.
现在最痛苦的时候已经过去了
And now the painful part's over.
我变得更加坚强
I've come out the other\nside a little bit stronger.
你们知道 我... \n我现在几乎都已经不再想她了
You know, I... I hardly\neven think about her anymore.
我想 这就是时间的力量
That's what time does, I guess.
Ted 昨天才举办的婚礼啊
Ted, the wedding was yesterday.
才过了24小时
It's been 24 hours.
我知道 只是我已经重新开始新的生活了
I know. And this is me, moving on.
我生命中的新篇章今天开始书写\n我们要庆祝一下
A great new chapte of my life began\ntoday, and we're gonna celebrate.
现在 我们需要库尔邦乐队\n(美国70年代最有影响力的Funk乐队)
Right now, we need two things. We\nneed Kool, and we need the Gang.
点唱时间到了 哈?
It's jukebox time, huh?
我看着那个年轻人扭着\n一路跳向点唱机
I look at that young man popping and\nlocking his way over to the jukebox,
我这么想着 你们知道...
and I think to myself, you know...
也许Stella做出了正确的选择
maybe Stella made the right call.
嗷 疼啊
Ow, pain.
他现在怎么能跳舞啊?
How is he dancing right now?
他应该...\n他应该用个大锤把Stella的车给砸了啊\n(损友损招 )
He should... he should be smashing\nup Stella's car with a sledgehammer.
假设一下哈
Hypothetical.
Ted并不是在假装开心
Ted isn't pretending to be happy.
Ted是真的很开心
Ted really is happy.
他根本不想结婚
He never wanted to get\nmarried in the first place.
有我的支持 \nTed摆脱了最沉重的负担
Ted just pulled off the greatest\ntrain dodge since Stand by Me.
那个拖油瓶还好说\n后面要生一堆孩子够他受的
Well, not the first\nkid, but the other kids.
不 他情况很糟糕
No, he is in bad shape.
怎么啦?
What's up?
真的很惨啊
Really bad shape.
我们要安慰他
And we need to be there for him.
虽然我的朋友们尽力安慰我
But as much as my friends\nwanted to be there for me,
但我 从任何方面来看 \n都好得不得了
I was, by all appearances, fine.
嘿 伙计 出去玩不?
Hey, buddy. Want to hang out?
老友们 我没事
Guys, I'm fine.
嘿 伙计 来接手几招吗?
Hey, pal, you want to have a catch?
我没事
I'm fine.
嘿 小子
Hey, kiddo.
Barney 我没事
Barney, I'm fine.
没必要这样 而且这太别扭啦
This is not necessary, and\nit's actually kind of weird.
没有冒犯的意思 女士们
No offense, ladies.
我不知道你在家
I did not realize you'd be home.
女士们 我们转战天井
Ladies, to the stairwell.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第6集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode06
最后 两周后\n这种无可避免的情绪发作了
Finally, after two weeks, the\ninevitable emotions boiled over.
嘿 你们想去吃晚饭吗?
Hey, you guys want to get some dinner?
哦 闭嘴
Oh, shut up.
对不起 亲爱的
I'm sorry, sweetie.
只是 Ted 你正承受着精神痛苦
It's just, Ted, you've been\nthrough something traumatic,
作为朋友 我们想要安慰你
and we're trying to be\nthere for you as friends,
但你拒绝我们 让我们滚开\n你个自私鬼
but you're not letting us, and it's\npissing us off, you selfish bitch.
抱歉
Sorry.
听着 我们只是担心\n你不能承受Stella这事的打击
Look, we're just worried that you're\nnot dealing with this whole Stella thing.
你还记得那时Lily离开我的情景吗?
Do you remember when Lily left me?
你还记得我那时怎么控制自己的情绪吗?
You remember how I held in my feelings?
我...非常...想她
I... miss... her so much.
耶 天啊 你可真是坚强啊
Yeah, dude, you were a rock.
嗯 我本该更落魄的 好吧?
Well, I should have\nbeen even worse, okay?
我本该疯了的
I should have gotten mad.
我本该听你的把Lily的东西都给烧了的
I should have taken your advice\nand set all of Lily's stuff on fire.
哦 好极了 多谢了 Ted
Oh, nice--\nthanks, Ted.
但我没有 \n我想这就是为什么我那么久才能恢复过来
But I didn't, and I think that that's\nwhy it took me so long to get better.
那么 现在 Ted...
So, now, Ted...
我想让你把悲苦都爆发出来
I want you to explode.
释放你的愤怒的狂暴武士吧 \n好吗 准备好了吗?
Release the berserker. Okay, ready?
现在!
Now!
- 我很好\n- 不
- I'm good.\n- No.
伙计们 饶了他吧 他现在很开心
Guys, get off his back. He's happy.
听着 如果Ted已经结婚了\n那么他就是结婚了的
Listen, if Ted were married\nright now, he'd be married,
他就要住在新泽西州\n他就是婚姻的囚徒
he'd be living in New\nJersey, and he'd be married.
他很好 那么 咱们开吃吧\n去Flat Michael's吃怎么样?
He's fine. Now, let's eat.\nHow about Flat Michael's?
不 那在44大街和Lex大街交叉处\n不能去那
No, that's 44th and Lex. Can't do it.
为什么?
Why not?
那儿太靠近Stella的健身馆了\n可能会碰见她
It's too close to Stella's\ngym. Might run into her.
还有别的地儿吗
Anywhere else, though.
好吧 嗯 那么Hurley's餐馆呢?
Okay, um, how about Hurley's?
就位于Stella的办公室和她去的干洗店之间\n不行
Right between Stella's office\nand her dry cleaners. No, sir.
好吧 那Meatloaf Charlie's餐馆呢?
Well, what about Meatloaf Charlie's?
那离Stella老妈去的理发店只有两条街区
Two blocks from Stella's\nmother's hairdressers.
好吧 Ted \n在曼哈顿还有我们能去吃饭的地儿吗?
Well, geez, Ted, is there anywhere\nin Manhattan we can go to dinner?
当然 我们来看看
Of course. Check this out.
你这哪来的 Ted?
What you got there, Ted?
我给自己做的"提醒"地图
A little reference\nmap I made for myself.
这是一张能指导大家不遇见\nStella Zinman的纽约城市指南
A New York guide to places you\nmight run into Stella Zinman.
红色区域是禁区
Red areas are places to avoid.
白色区域是安全地带
White areas are safe.
蓝色区域是水域
Blue is water.
- 太荒唐了\n- 但是 水域倒还真是蓝色的
- That is just ridiculous.\n- Well, water is blue.
你不能这样生活
You can't live that way.
是她在婚礼上撇下你走了\n而你却要回避她?
She leaves you at the altar,\nand you're the one avoiding her?
是的 我是在回避她\n有什么关系吗?
Yes, I'm avoiding her.\nWhat's the big deal?
我们就是这样做的
That's how we do it.
"我们"是谁 胆小鬼吗?
Who's we, gutless weenies?
才不是 "我们"是指\n从伟大的俄亥俄州来的人
Uh, no, "we" is people from\nthe great state of Ohio.
当生活的痛苦来临 我们七叶树州人\n(俄亥俄州人的别称)面对它 打压它
When life gives us pain, we Buckeyes\nta that pain and we push it down.
当痛苦再次来临 我们更多的打压它
And if the pain starts to come up again,\nwe push more pain down on top of it.
能避则避 干嘛要去犯事 对吧?
Why confront something when\nyou can avoid it, right?
我所能做的就是永不再见Stella\n这样我就能快乐幸福的生活了
All I have to do is never see Stella\nagain, and I'll live a long, happy life.
现在 谁想吃点什么东西吗?
Now, who wants to get something to eat?
哦 有人跟我推荐过一个好去处\n就在白色区域里
Oh, somebody just told me about a\ntapas place that's in the white zone.
不错 咱们就去那吧
Great. Let's go there.
想好点什么了吗?
You ready to order?
嗯 还没呢
Uh, not quite yet.
哦 我们能来点跟那桌一样的杏仁吗?
Oh, can we get some of\nthose almonds for the table?
当然可以
Certainly.
干得不错 Lily 这地方看起来不错
Nice call, Lily. This place looks great.
谁推荐给你的?
Who told you about it?
我不记得了
You know, I don't remember.
什么?
What?
我想起来了
I just remembered.
哦 天啊 哦 天啊
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
好吧 好吧 冷静点
Okay, okay, just be cool.
我们需要面对这事
We're just gonna have to deal with this.
大伙... 跟着我做
Everyone... follow my lead.
- 哦 你不是开玩笑吧\n- 他当真吗?
- Oh, you're kidding.\n- Is he serious?
我不要躲到这桌子底下
I am not getting under this table.
那桌还可以考虑一下
I'd maybe get under that table.
她转过来了
She's turning around.
想想 想想
Think,hink, think.
大伙待在这儿\n我去探探情况
Everyone, just stay here.\nI'm gonna go take a look.
Marshall去探探情况
Marshall, go take a look.
你需要餐具吗?
And will you need utensils?
不 我外带回家
No, I'm just going straight home.
她是要外卖带回家
She's placing an order to go.
她看着开心吗? 她提起我了吗?
Did she seem happy? Did\nshe say anything about me?
我才不关心呢
I don't even care.
我们的杏仁呢?
Where are those almonds?
啊呀 Ted这个傻瓜哪儿去了?
Gosh, where would Ted's nuts be?
嘿 建议你去Stella家车库的钳子里找找
Hey, why don't you check\nthe vise in Stella's garage.
快去对她宣泄一下你的怒火
Go yell at her.
Ted 也许你是从俄亥俄州来的\n但你现在住在纽约了呀
Ted, you may be from Ohio,\nbut you live in New York now.
在纽约我们不会压制情感的
We don't push down our\nfeelings in New York.
我们表现愤怒 一定给别人好看!
We take our feelings and we shove\nthem in somebody else's face!
哦 饶了我吧 Lily
Oh, spare me, Lily.
如果是你 你也会这样做的
You'd be doing the same thing\nif you were in this situation.
不可能
That's outrageous.
这世界上还无人能让我躲在这桌子底下的
There is not a person on Earth\nI would hide under a table from.
哦 真的 没有人吗?
Oh, really, not a single person?
甚至... 毒气工也不行?
Not even... Gasser?
你竟敢跟我提他
How dare you mention that name to me.
谁是毒气工?
Who's Gasser?
他是我最不想看见的人
He's the last person I'd want\nto see walk through that door.
Michael Sasser\nMichael Sasser.
他是我高中的同学
He's a guy I went to high school with.
新生生物课时 Michael坐在我旁边
Michael sat next to\nme in freshman biology.
他的初中过得有点失败
He had been a bit of a loser\nall through middle school,
但是在九年级 他一下子长高了12寸\n还参加了棒球队
but the summer before ninth grade, he grew\n12 inches and joined the baseball team.
他眼看就要变成风云人物了
He was right on the precipice\nof becoming one of the cool kids.
直到有一天...
Until one day...
哦 Lily 我们都经历过
Oh, Lily, we've all been there.
你放屁的时候 那可不是一般的难忍
When you've ripped one, it's not pretty.
你干了什么?
What did you do?
这还用问吗? 那可是九年级啊
Are you kidding? This was ninth grade.
我只有一个选择
I only had one choice.
哦 我的天啊 Sasser 这屁够响的啊?
Oh, my God, Sasser. Fart much?
不 不是我 是她放的
No, it wasn't me. It was her.
哦 装什么啊 Sasser\n你个毒气工
Oh, as if, Sasser. More like Gasser.
- 毒气工! 毒气工! 毒气工!\n- 不
- Gasser! Gasser! Gasser!\n- No.
- 毒气工!毒气工!毒气工! 毒气工! \n- 我参加棒球队呢 我-我酷着呢
- Gasser! Gasser! Gasser! Gasser! -\nI'm on the baseball team. I-I'm cool.
毒气工! 毒气工!
Gasser! Gasser!
毒气工这外号就这么叫下来了
The nickname Gasser stuck.
他总被嘲笑 最后不得不转学了
He got teased so much, eventually\nhe had to change schools.
这群孩子还真有一手
Kids are awesome.
我总为这事内疚
I've always felt awful about that.
但如果毒气工 不对 是Michael从那走进来\n不管怎么艰难
But if Gasser-- Michael-- walked in\nright now, as hard as it would be,
我也会走向毒气工 不对 是Michael\n了结了这件事
I would go up to Gasser-- Michael--\nand I would resolve things between us.
对 顿时神清气爽 宛如新生
Right, clear the air, as it were.
哦 伙计
Oh, man.
这种事罕有啊
Those don't come around often.
不怪你的
Y'all are welcome.
嘿 你们还好吧?
Hey, are you guys okay?
挺好 如果可以 我们想在这下面吃呢
Oh, yeah. We're just gonna be\neating down here if that's okay.
好吧 这是你的杏仁
Well, here's your almonds.
哦 谢谢... 你们今天有特价菜品推荐吗?
Oh, thanks... you guys\nhave any specials today?
Ted 这太可笑啦
Ted, this is ludicrous.
Ted 我是这样的人...
Ted, I am a person who...
好吧 让我们面对事实吧
well, let's just face it.
我不想遇上的人多着呢
There are a lot of people\nI don't want to see--
跟我睡过的那些妞儿们
people of the "chicks\nI banged" persuasion--
但是如果她们中的任何一个走进来的话
but if any of them were to walk in here,
我会站起来 直盯着她们的眼睛
I would stand up, and I would\nlook them right in the eye.
其中一些我们上床的时候\n我都没直视她眼睛呢
Some of them for the very first time.
真的 你真的谁都不躲吗?
Really, you wouldn't hide from anyone?
就连...Becca Delucci?
Not even, say... Becca Delucci?
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
谁是Becca Delucci?
Who's Becca Delucci?
你介意回避一下吗?
Do you mind?
好了 谁是Becca Delucci呢?
So, who is Becca Delucci?
Becca是个住在北部的女孩
Becca is just this\ngirl who lives upstate.
我以前常去造访她
I used to visit her now and again.
呒 北部具体哪里啊 Barney?
Mm-hmm, where exactly upstate, Barney?
贝德福德山联邦监狱
Bedford Hills Federal Penitentiary.
没错 我是以你丈夫的名义来看你的
And yes, the visits were\nof a conjugal nature.
- 没门 真的?\n- 真的
- No way, really?\n- Really.
我和Becca处得很好
And what I had with Becca\nwas a perfect relationship.
根据法律 她每周只允许给我打一次电话
She was only allowed, by\nlaw, to call me once a week.
她要是想多说一句\n武装守卫就会阻止她
If she ever got clingy, the\narmed guards stopped her.
我从来都不用为晚餐买单
And I never had to pay for dinner.
也不能这么说 我交了税
Well, that's not true. I pay taxes.
所以我觉得我们都要为吃饭付钱\n谢了 伙计们
Then again, I guess we all paid\nfor dinner. Thanks a lot, guys.
我最后一次去看她的时候\n貌似把事情搞砸了
Anyway, the last time I visited,\nI kind of screwed things up.
我知道很苦 宝贝儿\n我也在坐牢啊
I know it's hard, baby,\nbut I'm in a prison, too.
我心中的牢狱
A prison of my own heart.
现在有空房间吗 我们能... \n时间快到了?
Is that room ready yet or\nwhat? Can we... Tick-tock.
Barney 你是唯一能让我坚持下去的原因
Barney, you're the only thing\nthat's keeping me going here.
所以我来了 宝贝儿 \n我是你坚强的依靠 是... 天啊 你好 美女
That's what I'm here for, baby. I'm your\nrock. I'm... oh, my God. Hello, strange.
嗨 我是Barney Stinson律师
Barney Stinson, attorney at law.
我们来看看怎么让你出来吧
Let's talk about getting you off.
混蛋 不!
Oh, hell, no!
现在我收到Becca的来信 她完全疯了
Now I get letters from\nBecca and she's all,
我出来的那天会去找你
"I'm coming to get you\nthe day I get out of here.
我要把你的眼睛挖出来\n挂在我车子的后视镜上
I'm gonna hang your eyes\nfrom my rearview mirror."
女人啊
Women, huh?
看吧 你怕见到Becca \nLily怕见到毒气工
See? You're scared of Becca.\nLily's scared of Gasser.
我们继续躲着
We're staying under the table.
我们用不着躲了 Stella走了
We don't have to. Stella's gone.
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
终于没事了 这就是我们的俄亥俄风格
There, all done, and that's\nhow we do it Ohio style.
有情况出现 但我们避免了\n没问题了
Problem showed up. We\navoided it. It went away.
- 现在我们可以好好的享受大餐...\n- 她又回来了
- Now we can enjoy our meal in peace and...\n- She's back.
Ted 我们都觉得你必须...\n等等 Barney哪去了?
Ted, we all think that you\nneed-- wait, where's Barney?
Ted 我们都觉得你必须跟她谈谈
Ted, we all think that\nyou need to go talk to her.
- 我不觉得\n- 什么?
- I don't.\n- What?
要是我最不想见到的那个人进来了\n我绝不会跟他说一个字
Yeah, if the last person I wanted to see walked\nthrough the door, I wouldn't say a damn word.
- 是吗?\n- 是谁?
- Really?\n- And who's that?
我爸爸
My father.
伙计们 那张桌子游戏结束
You guys, that other\ntable is off the hook.
- 你们在谈什么?\n- Robin的爸爸
- What are we talking about?\n- Robin's dad.
我已经3年都没跟他说过话了\n现在也不打算说
I haven't spoken to him in three\nyears and I don't intend to start now.
为什么?
Why?
那得从我出生那天说起
It goes back to the day I was born.
把我儿子生出来 用力
You give me my son now. Push.
哦 不...不 不
Oh, no... oh, no.
他想要个儿子 但是个女儿的事实\n也没有改变他的计划
He wanted a son and the fact that\nI was a girl didn't change his plan.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我的全名是Robin Charles Scherbatsky Jr.
My full legal name is Robin\nCharles Scherbatsky, Jr.
但那只是灾难的开始
And it only gets worse from there.
我八岁时 他第一次带我去打猎
When I was eight, he took me\nhunting for the first time.
我不想去打小鹿
I don't want to shoot a deer.
胡说 R.J 射鹿是很高贵的消遣
Nonsense, R.J.Shooting deer\nis the noblest of pursuits.
但它们太可爱了
But they're cute.
你也这样说我们的兔子
You said the same\nthing about our rabbits.
还记得兔肉多好吃吧
Remember how delicious they were?
我发育的那些年
Over the years, as my body developed...
等会儿
Whoa, hold on a sec.
抱歉 继续说
Sorry, go on.
他更是想方设法假装我是个男孩
It became harder and harder\nfor him to pretend I was a boy.
最糟糕的时候是我刚满14岁时
The lowest moment came when I turned 14.
我们青少年冰球队刚赢了Squamish邀请赛
My peewee hockey team had just\nwon the Squamish Invitational
每个队员都来我家庆祝
and everyone came back\nto my house to celebrate.
你们这些孩子在比赛中表现得太棒了
You lads availed yourself\nsplendidly out there on the ice.
太棒了
Splendidly.
你们先出去玩
You go on outside.
我去拿些饮料 和椒盐脆饼来
I'll come back with an assortment\nof soft drinks and American pretzels.
我真不敢相信最后那个空门\n你也没打进 你个小姑娘
I can't believe you missed that\nlast empty-netter, you hoser.
你才是小姑娘
You're the hoser.
不 你才是小姑娘
No, you're the hoser.
你们在干什么?
What are you doing?
你们是队友 冰球手
You're teammates, hockey players.
队友是不可以接吻的!
Teammates don't kiss!
冰球手不可以接吻!
Hockey players don't kiss!
天啊 我没有儿子
Oh, my God. I have no son.
你真可怜
Oh, you poor thing.
旁边就是强大的美国\n但却偏偏出生在加拿大
To have to grow up in Canada\nwith America right there.
你爸真太过分了 Robin\n但祝贺你们赢了比赛
That... sucks about your dad, Robin,\nbut congratulations on that game.
Kyle和我并没有做什么
And Kyle and I weren't\neven doing anything serious.
我们只是到了蓝线
We only went to the blue line.
蓝线?
The blue line?
当你还是小孩子的时候 \n总是把什么事都用冰球术语表示
Yeah, you know how when you're a kid,\nyou put everything into hockey terms?
蓝线代表接吻\n红线就是脱光了
The blue line is kissing;\nthe red line is getting naked;
我想 在击球线 就不言而喻了
and I think "in the\ncrease" speaks for itself.
那之后 我和我爸就闹僵了
Anyway, after that, my relationship\nwith my dad pretty much went north.
我搬过去跟我妈妈住 留了长发\n成了加拿大流行歌手
I moved in with my mom, grew my\nhair out, became a Canadian pop star.
像普通的青年一样
You know, normal teen stuff.
你不觉得跟他说说这一切会舒服些吗
Don't you think it would feel\nbetter to talk to him about all this?
不 这是关键 这解决不了任何问题
No, that's the point. It\nwouldn't solve anything.
都是过去的事了 已经发生了
It's in the past. It's done.
那我能跟他说什么呢
I mean, what would I even say to him?
我希望你没有把我当个男孩子养
I wish you hadn't raised me as a boy?
我希望你没有教我打猎 \n钓鱼 抽烟 喝苏格兰威士忌
"I wish you hadn't taught me how to hunt\nand fish and smoke cigars and drink Scotch"
因为那不是女孩子做的事
"because that's not what girls do.
而我打球像个女孩子 \n也是因为 我就是个女孩子
And you know the reason I throw like\na girl, Dad," is because I am a girl."
你都憋了很久了吧
Wow, you held onto that\nfor a long time, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
让你很难受吧
It really messed you up.
- 是啊\n- 太糟糕了
- Yeah.\n- That sucks.
- 真遗憾\n- 挺热辣的
- I'm sorry.\n- That's hot.
然后我意识到...
And then I realized...
我所有的朋友都有心结\n但我的情况和他们有点不同
all of my friends were haunted, but there\nwas a difference between my ghost and theirs.
对我来说还不算晚
It wasn't too late for me.
我要过去跟她谈谈
I'm gonna go talk to her.
她走了 我去追她
She's gone. I'm going after her.
走 走
Go, go.
她往那走了!
There she goes!
计程车!
Taxi!
我看到她了 在我们前面 隔了两辆车\n往右开了
Okay, I see her. She's two\ncabs ahead on the right.
跟紧她 好吗?
Just stay with her, okay?
终于 你终于这么做了
Finally. Finally, you're doing this.
你要去面对她
You're going to confront her.
- 是的 我要面对她\n- 是的
- Yes, I am going to confront her.\n- Yeah.
- 太兴奋了\n- 绝对是的
- This is so exciting.\n- Totally.
你要说什么?
What are you going to say?
我会说 Stella \n很抱歉 我们没能结成婚
I'm gonna say, "Stella, I'm\nsorry things didn't work out."
- 天哪 不是吧\n- 不!
- Ay, caramba.\n- No!
我们要以成年人的方式交谈
Yes. We're going to talk\nabout this like adults.
她会说她的理由
She can tell me her side and...
而我 会听
I'm going to listen.
其实以前我们就应该更多的倾诉和倾听
Probably should have done a\nlittle more of that before.
司机 拜托带我们往最近的灯柱上撞吧?
Driver, can you run us\ninto the nearest lamppost?
大家系好安全带 除了你 Ted
Everyone, buckle up. Not you, Ted.
Ted Ted 是你发泄愤怒的时候了
Ted, Ted, you got to get mad right now.
拜托 挖掘内心的怒火
Come on. Dig deep.
伙计 拜托 关键不是我捶胸顿足 \n暴跳如雷
Dude, come on. This isn't about me waving my\narms, stamping my feet, and getting really mad.
关键是我和Stella终于要交流一下了
This is about Stella and\nI finally communicating.
- 很明显 那...\n- Stella讨厌星战
- I mean, clearly, that was...\n- Stella hated Star Wars.
她欺骗了你 跟着你的感觉走 Ted
She lied to you. Search\nyour feelings, Ted.
你知道我说的是真的
You know it to be true.
那是她的事
Well, that's her business.
拜托 Ted 她在婚礼时离开了你
Come on, Ted. She left you at the altar.
- 我真不明白!\n- Ted 你想想那多恶劣啊...
- I don't understand!\n- Ted, in the name of all that is sacred...
等等 等等! 她往哪去了?
Wait, wait, wait! Where is she going?
她的车在林肯隧道转弯了
Her cab just missed the\nturn for the Lincoln Tunnel.
为什么有人买了外卖还带到新泽西?
Why would anybody buy takeout food and bring\nit all the way back to New Jersey anyway?
也许是去她的办公室
Maybe she's going to her office.
不是
No.
服务员问她 你要餐具吗
The waiter asked her,\n"Will you need utensils?"
她回答说 不 我直接回家
and then she said, "Nah, I'm\njust going straight home."
但要是她回家 为什么还来...
But if she's going home,\nwhy are we still heading...
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
Tony住在市中心
Tony lives downtown.
她所说的家是指Tony公寓
Home is Tony's apartment.
她要我搬到新泽西\n而她自己却搬到市里跟Tony住?
She was going to make me move to New Jersey\nand then she moves into the city with Tony?
贱人!
Son of a bitch!
终于 终于明白了吧 老兄
Finally. Finally, buddy.
- 我现在非常生气!\n- 我就喜欢这样!
- I am so angry right now!\n- I know, and I love it!
太棒了!
Yeah, that is awesome!
先生 我们很乐意付车窗摇杆的钱
Sir, we'd be happy to cover\nthe cost of that window crank.
我喜欢愤怒的Ted!
I love angry Ted!
我也是!
So do I!
说出来 喊出来 发泄出来
Get it out, baby. Let it out.
她停车了
she's stopping.
就是现在了 我要爆发了!
Oh, it is on. It is on!
Ted 上去和她说清楚 老兄!
Yes, Ted. Go get her, buddy!
甩掉你的胆怯!
Go get rid of your demons!
我的腿都挤麻了!
My leg is asleep!
等等 等等 别急
Okay, wa-wa-wait.\nWait, hold on.
- Lily 你干嘛呢?\n- 等一下 别急
- Lily, what are you doing?\n- All right, hold on.
Ted 你现在发怒了很好
Look, Ted, it's great that\nyou're angry right now.
- 当然\n- 是的
- It sure is.\n- Yes.
你终于要面对了 但你只有一次机会
And that you're finally dealing with\nthis, but you only get one shot here.
我们得讨论一下 你该说些什么
Let's just take a beat and, and\nthink about what you're going to say.
我很清楚我要说什么
Oh, I know exactly what I'm gonna say.
你选错人了
You picked the wrong guy.
Ted\nTed.
你选错人了
You picked the wrong guy.
你做了一个非常 非常错误的选择
You made a really,\nreally, really bad choice.
你在想什么?
What were you thinking?
那男的? 你在耍我吧?
That guy? Are you kidding me?
过去的八年里 你都没认识到什么吗?
Have you learned nothing\nin the last eight years?
你一定会后悔 对吧
You're just gonna regret\nthis. You know that, right?
你会后悔的 但你什么都做不了 \n一切都太迟了
You are going to regret this, and now there is\nnothing you can do about it because it's too late.
你所能做的就是上去 \n开始你糟糕的 令人失望的生活
All you can do now is go up there and\nstart your crappy, disappointing life
一丁点都比不上和我在一起的幸福
that will never be nearly as happy\nas the one you could have had with me.
再见了
Good-bye.
Ted 等等
Ted, wait.
Stella 我来这不是要把你抢回来
Look, Stella, I am not\nhere to win you back.
我来这是确认你意识到 \n你犯了人生中最大的错
I am here because I need to know that you\nknow you made the biggest mistake of your life.
我知道
I know.
很好
Good.
这就是我要说的
That's what I'm gonna say.
真狠! 真冷血
Ooh, dag! Cold-blooded.
那很好 去 就这么说
Yeah, that's good. Go say that.
谢谢
Thanks.
我下了车 准备说那些话\n准备爆发 但是...
So I got out of the cab, ready to say all\nof that stuff, ready to explode, but then...
妈妈!
Mommy!
却都泡汤了
It all just went away.
事情就是那样
And that was it.
那时候 我一点也不生气了
In that moment, I wasn't angry anymore.
我知道Stella注定要和Tony在一起
I could see Stella was\nmeant to be with Tony.
孩子们 也许你们以为只有两条路\n忍气吞声 或者把气撒在别人身上
Kids, you may think your only choices are to\nswallow your anger or throw it in someone's face.
其实还有第三种选择\n让它过去
There's a third option:\nyou can just let it go,
也只有你这样做了 它才真的消失\n你才可以开始新的生活
and only when you do that is it\nreally gone, and you can move forward.
孩子们 这才是最完美的爱情故事\n最完美的结局
And that, kids, was the perfect\nending to a perfect love story.
只是没找对人
It just wasn't mine.
我的爱还在某个地方等着我
Mine was still out there waiting for me.